Guide to the Facilities Management Department records, 1924-ongoing UA.10.05.0002
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Facilities Management Department records
1925-ongoing
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University. Facilities Management Department
UA.10.05.0002
36 Linear Feet
3.1 Gigabytes
The Facilities Management Department (FMD) is responsible for the maintenance, repair and minor alteration of the campus facilities. Collection contains material pertaining to the operations of the Facilities Management Department (FMD) including a 1990/1991 annual report, committee minutes, materials related to the restoration of the stained glass windows in the Chapel, and architectural drawings from the Trumbauer firm of many campus buildings.
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
For a period of twenty-five years from the origin of the material, permission in writing from the office of origin and the University Archivist is required for use. After twenty-five years, records that have been processed may be consulted with the permission of the University Archivist.
Electronic records in this series have been migrated to a library server and digital use copies can only be accessed onsite in the Rubenstein Library Reading Room. To request access, please contact Research Services before coming to use these records.
Provenance
The Facilities Management Department records were received by the University Archives as a transfer in 1995-2006, 2008, 2010, 2017, and 2018.
Historical Note
The Facilities Management Department (FMD) is responsible for the maintenance, repair and minor alteration of the campus facilities. FMD employees are ready to respond to urgent or specialized needs, and provide valuable service for basic maintenance and repair programs. They are also able to provide timely and flexible renovation services of moderate scope. FMD has also been known as Facilities Planning and Management.
Several campus buildings have undergone name changes since construction, such as the naming of the Indoor Staidum as Cameron Indoor Stadium, and the Gymnasium Building as Card Gym. In 1930, the Classroom Building was named the Carr Building, for Julian S. Carr, in recognition of his gifts to then-Trinity College. In 2018, the Board of Trustees voted to remove Carr's name from the building on the recommendation of a committee formed by President Vince Price at the request of the Department of History, based on acknowledgement of Carr's white supremacist activities and views.
Collection Overview
Collection contains material pertaining to the operations of the Facilities Management Department (FMD). Materials include the 1990/1991 annual report, committee minutes, significant materials related to the restoration of the Duke Chapel stained glass windows, including condition reports by Dieter Goldkuhle, color slides of the conservation, and rubbings of the windows, as well as original architectural drawings of many campus buildings created by the Horace Trumbauer Firm, for which African American architect Julian Abele was the chief designer.
Separated Material
Chapel window rubbings are stored separately in the library stacks. A zip drive containing jpeg images of the restoration of window #212 and #223 were separated and the images were downloaded onto the digital server.
Related Material
Thomas E. Dixon Papers, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Horace Trumbauer Architectural Drawings Collection, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
University Architect Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Duke Chapel (Durham, N.C.); Glass, colored -- Conservation and restoration; Rubbing (transferring techniques); Color slides; Glass painting and staining -- Conservation and restoration; Color photographs; Architectural drawing -- North Carolina; College buildings -- North Carolina; College buildings -- Designs and plans; Duke University -- Administration; Sanford, Terry; Duke University. Office of the Executive Vice President; Trumbauer, Horace, 1869-1938; Abele, Julian, 1881-1950
- General Files, 3 boxes
  Scope and Contents
  Includes the 1990/1991 annual report, committee minutes, and a current replacement audit value (1991). Many of the materials in this series relate to the the main subject present in the collection is the restoration of the Duke Chapel stained glass windows. Each restored window contains a condition report by Dieter Goldkuhle and color slides of the conservation. Rubbings have also been made of the Chapel windows and they are housed in the vault. Also present is a volume with text and photographs that document the Chapel Crypt opening and closing guide in preparation for Terry Sanford's internment.
  Conditions Governing Access
  [Electronic records in this series have been migrated to a library server and digital use copies can only be accessed onsite in the Rubenstein Library Reading Room. To request access, please contact Research Services before coming to use these records.]
  - Annual Report, 1990/1991, cuid0 (Box 1)
  - Banner Committee, 1996 (re: placement of banners on Duke University campus), cuid1 (Box 1)
  - Current Replacement Value (CRV) Audit, July 1991, cuid2 (Box 1)
  - Restoration slides and report, Ruth and Naomi windows #201 and #202, Duke Chapel, April 1994, cuid3 (Box 1)
  - Restoration slides and report, Adam window #205, Duke Chapel, August 1995 (3 folders), cuid4 (Box 1)
  - Restoration slides and report, Noah window #206, Duke Chapel, September 2002 (3 folders), cuid5 (Box 1)
  - Restoration slides and report, Melchezedek window, #207, Duke Chapel, August 2003(3 folders), cuid6 (Box 2)
  - Restoration slides and report, Abraham window #208, Duke Chapel, August 2004 (3 folders), cuid7 (Box 2)
  - Restoration slides and report, Isaac window #209, Duke Chapel, August 2006 (3 folders), cuid8 (Box 2)
  - Restoration slides and report, South-West Transept (Joseph, Gabriel, Mary, Elijah, Elisha, Hezekiah) window #211, Duke Chapel, August 2005 (3 folders), cuid9 (Box 2)
  - Restoration slides and report, Panel A3 window #227, Duke Chapel, January 2001, cuid10 (Box 2)
  - Restoration slides and report, Tobit window #228, Duke Chapel, September 2000, (2 folders), cuid11 (Box 3)
  - Restoration slides and report, Tobit window #228, Duke Chapel, Appendix A, (2 folders), cuid12 (Box 3)
  - Crypt Opening/Closing Procedure Guide, 1998, cuid13 (Box 3)
  - Restoration photos, Window #210, Duke Chapel, 2008; cuid172
    292 JPG images; approximately 717 megabytes.
    [Restricted until 2033.]
  - Restoration Report: Window #212, April 2010, cuid14 (Box 3)
  - Restoration photos and report, Window #212, Duke Chapel, 2009-2010; cuid173; 376 JPG images; approximately 1.5 gigabyte.
    [Restricted until 2035.]
  - Restoration Report: Window #223, April 2011, cuid15 (Box 3)
  - Restoration photos, Window #223, Duke Chapel, 2010-2011; cuid171; 203 JPG images; approximately 800 megabytes.
    [Restricted until 2036.]
  - Chapel windows #s 201 (Ruth), 204, 205 (Adam), 228 (Tobit), cuid16 (Box 3)
  - Noah window, #206, cuid17 (Box 3)
  - Melchezedek window, #207, cuid18 (Box 3)
  - Abraham window, #208, cuid19 (Box 3)
  - Isaac window, #209, cuid20 (Box 3)
  - Rubbing/leading guides Chapel window, #210, cuid21 (Box 3)
  - Panel and Trefoil rubbings/leading guides, #211, cuid22 (Box 3)
  - Restoration reports, Window #214, #218, Duke Chapel, 2015-2016; cuid170; 2 PDF documents; approximately 158 megabytes.
- Architectual Drawings, 2
  Includes original architectural drawings of campus buildings from the Horace Trumbauer Firm, for which African American architect Julian Abele was the chief designer. Drawings depict floor plans, elevations, plumbing systems, electrical systems, and other aspects of building design and construction. These drawings were the reference copies kept by the Facilities Management Department, were heavily used, and may be in fragile condition.
  - Baldwin Auditorium
    Biographical / Historical
    31 sheets
    - Baldwin Auditorium, cuid174; 31 Sheets (Oversize-folder 43)
  - Brown Residence Hall
    25 sheets
    - Brown Residence Hall, cuid175; 25 Sheets (Oversize-folder 41)
  - Cameron Indoor Stadium (originally Indoor Stadium), 1
    - Indoor Stadium: First Floor Plan; Second Floor Plan; Balcony Floor Plan; Roof Plan; East and West Elevations (copy), 1940 January 22; cuid23; 7 Sheets (Oversize-folder 1)
      White paper copy; sheet numbers: 1-7
    - Proposed Indoor Stadium: Ground Floor Plan, 1939 March 17; cuid24; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 1)
      Blueprint
    - Proposed Indoor Stadium: Section thru End Bay, 1939 March 14; cuid25; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 1)
    - Proposed Indoor Stadium, undated; cuid26; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 1)
    - Door Schedule, 1939 July 18; cuid27; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 1)
    - Indoor Stadium, 1939 September 18; cuid28; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 1)
    - Indoor Stadium: First Floor Plan; Second Floor Plan; Balcony Floor Plan; Roof Plan; East and West Elevations (original), 1940 January 22; cuid29; 7 Sheets (Oversize-folder 1)
      Sheet numbers: 1-7
  - Card Gym (originally Gymnasium Building), 2
    - Approved Sketch Showing Location of Gymnasium, 1928 October 30; cuid30; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 2)
    - Interior Door Schedule, 1929 September 5; cuid31; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 2)
    - Gymansium Building, undated; cuid32; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 2)
    - Gymnasium: Floor plans, framing plans, 1930 January; cuid33; 13 Sheets (Oversize-folder 2)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 2597
    - Gymnasium: First floor plan, 1929 June 29; cuid34; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 2)
    - Gymnasium: Second floor plan, 1929 June 29; cuid35; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 2)
  - Classroom Building
    Formerly the Carr Building. See Historical note for more information.
    - Classroom Building 1 of 3, cuid176; 16 Sheets (Oversize-folder 31)
      16 sheets
    - Classroom Building 2 of 3, cuid177; 26 Sheets (Oversize-folder 32)
      26 sheets
    - Classroom Building 3 of 3, cuid178; 22 Sheets (Oversize-folder 33)
      22 sheets
  - Chapel, 3
    - Preliminary Plans of Chapel: Basement; First Floor Plans, undated; cuid36; 4 Sheets (Oversize-folder 3)
  - Craven Quad, 4
    - Group "A" Dormitories Addition: Interior Door Schedule, 1930 January 28; cuid37; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 4)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 6069
    - Group "A" Dormitories Addition: Floor Plans; Elevation, 1930 January 24; cuid39; 8 Sheets (Oversize-folder 4)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 6001-6008
    - Group "A" Dormitories Addition: Framing Plans, 1929 October 22; cuid40; 5 Sheets (Oversize-folder 4)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 6013-6017
    - Group "A" Dormitories Addition: Floor Plans, 1929 December 18; cuid41; 5 Sheets (Oversize-folder 4)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 6059-6063
    - Group "A" Dormitories: Floor Plans, 1929 November 12; cuid45; 5 Sheets (Oversize-folder 5)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 3501-3505
    - Group "A" Dormitories: Framing Plans; Plumbing, Heating, and Electrical Work, 1929 February 19; cuid46; 8 Sheets (Oversize-folder 5)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 3508-3515
  - Crowell Quad, 5
    - Group "B" Dormitories, undated; cuid167; 3 Sheets (Oversize-folder 7)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 26-28
    - Group "B" Dormitories: Clock Dial Layout, 1930 May 24; cuid38; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 6)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 4054
    - Group "B" Dormitory Court: Floor Plans; Elevation, 1930 April [?]; cuid47; 8 Sheets (Oversize-folder 6)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 6501-6508
    - Group "B" Dormitory Court: Floor Plans, 1930 January 6; cuid48; 4 Sheets (Oversize-folder 6)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 5629-5632
    - Spec. 24" D.F. Skeleton Dial Chain Suspended Sec. Clock, 1930 June 26; cuid49; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 7)
    - Group "B" Dormitories: Floor Plans; Heating, Plumbing, and Electrical Work, 1929 November 15; cuid51; 4 Sheets (Oversize-folder 7)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 4001-4002, 4005-4006
    - Group "B" Dormitories, cuid52 (Oversize-folder 7)
  - Duke Homestead, 6
    - Duke Homestead, 1935 April 13; cuid82; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 30)
  - Faculty Houses, 7
    - Faculty House A, 1931 June 3; cuid83; 4 Sheets (Oversize-folder 11)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 1-2
    - Faculty House no. 12, undated; cuid84; 4 Sheets (Oversize-folder 11)
    - Faculty House no. 11, 1930 March 3; cuid85; 2 Sheets (Oversize-folder 11)
    - Faculty House no. 9, 1930 April 12; cuid86; 5 Sheets (Oversize-folder 11)
    - Faculty House no. 8, 1930 April 11; cuid87; 2 Sheets (Oversize-folder 11)
    - Faculty House no. 6: Main Entrance and Hood, 1930 July 15; cuid88; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 11)
    - Faculty Houses no. 6 - 9 - 8, 1930 August 4; cuid89; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 11)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 5
    - Faculty Houses no. 6-8, 9-11, 1930 August 5; cuid90; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 11)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 6
    - Faculty House no. 6, 1930 June 2; cuid91; 2 Sheets (Oversize-folder 11)
    - Faculty House no. 1, 1931 February 9; cuid92; 7 Sheets (Oversize-folder 12)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 1-7
    - Faculty House D (Faculty House no. 7), 1931 June 10; cuid93; 4 Sheets (Oversize-folder 12)
    - Faculty House no. 4, 1930 April 30; cuid94; 4 Sheets (Oversize-folder 12)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 1-4
    - Faculty House no. 3, 1930 April 21; cuid95; 4 Sheets (Oversize-folder 12)
      Blueprint and white paper copy; sheet numbers: 1-4
    - Faculty House no. 2, 1931 September 20; cuid96; 7 Sheets (Oversize-folder 12)
  - Few Quad, 8
    - House I Electric Wiring, 1961 May 17; cuid97; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 13)
      White paper drawing
    - Proposed New Social Room for House FF, 1958 July 22; cuid98; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 13)
    - Proposed New Social Room for House FF, 1958 July 22; cuid99; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 13)
    - Group "D" Dormitories, 1938 July 1; cuid100; 5 Sheets (Oversize-folder 14)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 6-10
    - Group "D" Dormitories: Plumbing, Heating, and Electrical Work, 1938 July 18; cuid101; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 14)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: M1
    - Group "D" Dormitories: Layout of Underground Piptes, undated; cuid102; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 14)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 29
    - Group "D" Dormitories: Interior Door Schedule, 1938 July 15; cuid103; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 14)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 115
    - Group "D" Dormitories: Plumbing, Heating, and Electrical Work, 1938 June 7; cuid104; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 14)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: M4
    - Group "D" Dormitories: Plumbing, Heating, and Electrical Work, 1938 July 18; cuid105; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 14)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: M5
    - Group "D" Dormitories: Plumbing, Heating, and Electrical Work, 1938 August 25; cuid106; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 14)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: M2
    - Group "D" Dormitories: Plumbing, Heating, and Electrical Work, 1938 June 21; cuid107; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 14)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: M3
    - Group "D" Dormitories, 1938 September 29; cuid108; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 14)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 2
    - Group "D" Dormitories, 1938 September 29; cuid109; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 14)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 3
    - Group "D" Dormitories, 1938 September 29; cuid110; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 14)
    - Group "D" Dormitories, 1939 September 29; cuid111; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 14)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 4
  - Flowers/Page Auditorium (originally Classroom and Auditorium Building), 9
    - Classroom and Auditorium Building, 1930 June 27; cuid112; 6 Sheets (Oversize-folder 15)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 2561-2564
    - Classroom and Auditorium Building, 1929 December 16; cuid113; 7 Sheets (Oversize-folder 15)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 2501-2507
    - Classroom and Auditorium Building, 1930 March 30; cuid114; 12 Sheets (Oversize-folder 15)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 2501-2507, 2575, 2509-2512
    - Classroom and Auditorium Building, 1930 June 27; cuid115; 4 Sheets (Oversize-folder 15)
    - Auditorium: floor plans and elevations, 1925 July 24; cuid116; 10 Sheets (Oversize-folder 15)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 2564
  - Friedl Bulding
    32 sheets
    - Friedl Bulding, cuid179; 32 Sheets (Oversize-folder 42)
  - Giles, Alspaugh, Pegram, and Bassett
    - Giles, Alspaugh, Pegram, and Bassett 1 of 4, cuid180; 22 Sheets (Oversize-folder 37)
    - Giles, Alspaugh, Pegram, and Bassett 2 of 4, cuid181; 18 Sheets (Oversize-folder 38)
      18 sheets
    - Giles, Alspaugh, Pegram, and Bassett 3 of 4, cuid182; 33 Sheets (Oversize-folder 39)
      33 sheets
    - Giles, Alspaugh, Pegram, and Bassett 4 of 4, cuid183; 5 Sheets (Oversize-folder 40)
      5 sheets
  - Gray/Divinity School (originally School of Religion Building), 10
    See also Sociology/Psychology, which includes one sheet of School of religion drawings.
    - School of Religion Building: Tunnel; Basement; First; Second; Third Floor Plans; Elevation, 1930 August 5; cuid117; 7 Sheets (Oversize-folder 16)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 1501-1507
    - School of Religion Building: Detail of Chapel, 1929 July 4; cuid118; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 16)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 1533
    - School of Religion Building: Plumbing, Heating, and Electrical Work, 1929 November 28; cuid119; 5 Sheets (Oversize-folder 16)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 1539-1543
    - Interior Elevations of Chapel, 1929 July 4; cuid120; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 16)
    - Divinity Library General Reading Room, [1969] May 15; cuid121; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 16)
  - Hudson Hall (originally College of Engineering), 11
    - College of Engineering: Attic Floor Plan - Showing proposed wire and tile enclosure walls, 1950 March 13; cuid53; 2 Sheets (Oversize-folder 8)
    - College of Engineering: Ground Floor Plan, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Loft Floor and Roof Plan, 1947 January 6; cuid54; 4 Sheets (Oversize-folder 8)
    - College of Engineering: Elevations, Exterior Details, Typical Details, 1947 January 6; cuid55; 5 Sheets (Oversize-folder 8)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 5-9
    - College of Engineering: Details of Library, 1946 May 1; cuid56; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 8)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 15
    - College of Engineering: Details of Spandrels, Lintels and Elevator Penthouse; Spandrel and Lintel Details, 1946 April 20; cuid57; 2 Sheets (Oversize-folder 8)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 16-17
    - College of Engineering: FS Flat Brick Arch at Ground Floor Windows, 1946 April 20; cuid58; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 8)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 18
    - College of Engineering: Stairs, 1946 October 25; cuid59; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 8)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 19
    - College of Engineering: Details of Main Entrance, 1946 April 20; cuid60; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 8)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 20
    - College of Engineering: Toilet Room Details, 1946 July 24; cuid61; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 9)
    - College of Engineering: FS Section thru Sill, FS Detail of Slide-up Sash, 1946 August 7; cuid62; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 9)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 31
    - College of Engineering: Revised Plan of Elevator Penthouse Showing Ladder Opening, 1946 June 21; cuid63; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 9)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 32
    - College of Engineering: Revised Detail of Stairs in Mechanical Lab, 1946 August 5; cuid64; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 9)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 33
    - College of Engineering: Wrought Iron Grille in Transom Door, 1946 September 23; cuid65; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 9)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 34
    - College of Engineering: Detail thru Spandrel between Columns no. 92, 93, 94, and 95, 1946 August 29; cuid66; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 9)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 35
    - College of Engineering: Detail of Elevator Pit, 1946 September 5; cuid67; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 9)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 36
    - College of Engineering: Detail of Elevator Hoistway and Revised Elevator Penthouse, 1946 September 6; cuid68; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 9)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 37
    - College of Engineering: Plan thru Spandel, Detail of Angle Iron Spandrels Where Quoins Occur, 1946 September 23; cuid69; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 9)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 38
    - College of Engineering: Details of Miscellaneous Counters, Shelving, and Woven Wire Scrren Partitions; Elevations of Borrowed Lights and Dark Room Maze; Miscellaneous Millwork, 1946 October 7; cuid70; 3 Sheets (Oversize-folder 9)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 39-41
    - College of Engineering: Details of Library, 1946 October 15; cuid71; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 9)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 42
    - College of Engineering: Detail Showing Termination of Celotex Ceiling at West Stairs, 1946 October 29; cuid72; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 9)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 43
    - College of Engineering: Detail of New Junction Box Closet, 1946 November 8; cuid73; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 9)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 45
    - College of Engineering: Elevation of Woven Wire Screen in Room no. 021, 1947 February 12; cuid74; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 9)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 48
    - College of Engineering: Section thru Wall of Main Building at High Voltage Rm. Roof, 1947 March 26; cuid75; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 9)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 49
    - College of Engineering: Elevator Penthouse Framing, 1947 February 25; cuid76; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 9)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 50
    - College of Engineering: Full Size Detail Showing Head Section of Window if 3/8" Angle Lintels Are Used, 1946 August 5; cuid77; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 9)
    - College of Engineering: Details of Copper Pan at Ground Floor Windows and Copper Cap on Exterior Doors Swinging Out, 1947 March 27; cuid78; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 9)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 52
    - College of Engineering: Electrical Plans, 1946 May 1; cuid79; 4 Sheets (Oversize-folder 9)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: E1-E4
    - College of Engineering: Plumbing Plans; Heating Plans, 1946 May 1; cuid80; 9 Sheets (Oversize-folder 9)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: P1-P5, H1-H4
    - College of Engineering: Exterior Door Details; Full Size Details of Portico Stonework; Full Size Details of Stone Window Sills; Limestone Details; FS Head and Sill Window; FS Detail Door; FS Detail of Dormer Windows; FS Detail Brick Arch over Windows, 1946 June 4; cuid81; 8 Sheets (Oversize-folder 10)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 21-28
  - Jarvis Hall
    - Jarvis Hall, cuid184; 14 Sheets (Oversize-folder 34)
      14 sheets
  - Kilgo Quad, 12
    - Group "C" Dormitories, 1928 September 22; cuid166; 5 Sheets (Oversize-folder 31)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 6-9, 11
    - Group "C" Dormitories: Framing; Floor Plans, 1927 November 29; cuid50; 7 Sheets (Oversize-folder 31)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 13-19
    - Group "C" Dormitories: Basement; First; Third Floor Plans; Roof Plans, 1929 April 2; cuid42; 4 Sheets (Oversize-folder 31)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 1-2, 4-5
    - Group "C" Dormitories: Interior Details, 1927 October 21; cuid43; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 31)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 10
    - Group "C" Dormitories: First Floor Framing, 1927 October 21; cuid44; 1 Sheets (Oversize-folder 31)
      Blueprint; sheet numbers: 12
  - Language (also called Old Law, originally Law School Building), 13